A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25 (A99) FA477
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25 (A99)
1974-1999
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA477
99.6 Cubic Feet
83 standard record storage cartons. Boxes R3191-R3252, R3266-R3286.
Other Finding Aids note
For other open RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA479 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-1.15
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA471 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1999.
Arrangement note
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Biographical/Historical note
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Rockefeller Foundation
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A99), 1974-1999; 1.25; 99.6 Cubic Feet; 83 standard record storage cartons. Boxes R3191-R3252, R3266-R3286.
  Arrangement
  Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
  Portions of the material are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 86054 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - STAFF REBUILDING, 1986, 1989 (Box R3191)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 86054 A 1 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - FACULTY DEVELOPMENT, 1986-1996 (Box R3191)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2017. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 87050 - YESHIVA UNIVERSITY- MOLECULAR GENETICS OF MYCOBACTERIA, 1986-1996 (Box R3191)
    - RF 88072 - VOICE FOR AFRICA IN THE U.S., 1987-1992, 1998 (Box R3191)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2019. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 88072 - VOICE FOR AFRICA IN THE U.S. - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3191)
    - RF 88073 - BEYOND CHILD SURVIVAL, 1987-1989 April (Box R3192)
    - RF 88073 - BEYOND CHILD SURVIVAL, 1989 May-1995 (Box R3192)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2016. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 89026 A 35 - BANGLADESH RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE, 1989-1997 (Box R3192)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2018. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 89028 A 214 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - ANTI-MALARIAL CHEMOPROPHYLAXIS, 1989-1994, 1998 (Box R3192)
    - RF 89057 A 131 - UDGAONKAR, JAYANT B., 1990-1998 (Box R3192)
    - RF 89064 A 35 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA-FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAM EVALUATION IN VIETNAM, 1992-1995 (Box R3192)
    - RF 89064 A 36 - UNITED NATIONS FUND FOR POPULATION ACTIVITIES - CONTRACEPTIVES REQUIREMENTS & LOGISTIC MANAGEMENT NEEDS, 1991-1997 (Box R3192)
    - RF 89073 A 1 - SOUTHERN CONNECTICUT STATE UNIVERSITY - CONSORTIUM FOR URBAN EDUCATION, 1989-1995 (Box R3192)
    - RF 90003 A 466 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - RESIDENT FELLOWS (CHICANO STUDIES), 1989-1994 (Box R3193)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2015. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 90003 A 468 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1987-1998 (Box R3193)
    - RF 90030 A 1 - UNITED NATIONS INDUSTRIAL DEVELOPMENT ORGANIZATION - GALL MIDGE INSECT RESISTANCE, 1990-1996 (Box R3193)
    - RF 90032 A 73 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - GENE TRANSFORMATION OF RICE, 1990-1996 (Box R3193)
    - RF 90038 A 178 - SOl, REUBEN KIPNGENO, 1990-1998 (Box R3193)
    - RF 960064 - MEET THE COMPOSER - COMPOSERS-IN-RESIDENCE, 1980-1996 (Box R3194)
    - RF 960064 - MEET THE COMPOSER - COMPOSERS-IN-RESIDENCE, 1980-1996 (Box R3194)
    - RF 960064 - MEET THE COMPOSER - COMPOSERS-IN-RESIDENCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3195)
    - RF 90075 A 1 - UNIVERSITY OF MEXICO - GENE AMPLIFICATION IN RHIIZOBIUM, 1990-1997 (Box R3195)
    - RF 90075 A 1 - UNIVERSITY OF MEXICO - GENE AMPLIFICATION IN RHIIZOBIUM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3195)
    - RF 90080 A 18 - UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON - NAIROBI CHILDREN AND HIV MOTHERS, 1990-1998 (Box R3196)
    - RF 90091 A 9 - TROPICAL DISEASES RESEARCH CENTER (ZAMBIA) - SCHOOLING AND MATERIAL BEHAVIOR IN A ZAMBIAN TOWNSHIP, 1991-1994 (Box R3196)
    - RF 91001 A 138 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - RICE MAPPING, 1986-1998 (Box R3196)
    - RF 91003 A 112 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY DEVELOPMENT, 1989-1997 (Box R3196)
    - RF 91003 A 128 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY BASED DETECTION OF RICE TUNGRO VIRUSES, 1989-1997 (Box R3196)
    - RF 91009 A 7 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY- CONFERENCE: HERBICIDE USE IN ASIAN RICE PRODUCTION, 1992-1995 (Box R3197)
    - RF 91009 A 8 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - EFFECTS OF PESTICIDES ON THE IMMUNE SYSTEM, 1994-1997 (Box R3197)
    - RF 91013 A 481 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SANTA CRUZ) - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1991-1998 (Box R3197)
    - RF 91013 A 482 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS (AFRO-AMERICAN STUDIES), 1991-1994, 1997 (Box R3197)
    - RF 91013 A 484 - UNIVERSITY OF ROCHESTER - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1991-1996; 2 folders. (Box R3197)
    - RF 91013 A 485 - UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1991-1995 (Box R3197)
    - RF 91013 A 486 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - RESIDENT FELLOWS (HUMANITIES), 1990-1997 (Box R3198)
    - RF 91013 A 489 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1988-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3198)
    - RF 91025 A 93 - NEW HAVEN PUBLIC SCHOOLS - MIDDLE SCHOOLS RESTRUCTURING MODEL, 1991-1995 (Box R3198)
    - RF 91029 A 10 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - TRANSFORRMATION OF CASSAVA USING AGROBACTERIUM STRAINS, 1992-1996 (Box R3198)
    - RF 91032 A 3 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY, 1988-1996 (Box R3198)
    - RF 91033 - UNITED NATIONS - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SAFE MOTHERHOOD INITIATIVE, 1986-1995; 2 folders. (Box R3199)
    - RF 91035 A 9 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - CORE SUPPORT, 1991-1994 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91035 A 11 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - ELECTRICAL ENERGY EFFICIENCY FOR ZIMBABWE STUDY, 1992-1998 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91037 A 231 - WOLDE-MEDHIN, TESFAYE, 1991-1993 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91037 A 240 - MOYO, NGONIDZASHE - AFRICAN DISSERTATION INTERNSHIP AWARD, 1991-1994 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91037 A252 - OBURA, DAVID - ADIA: REEF CORALS IN KENYA, 1991-1997 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91042 - TELEVISION TRUST FOR THE ENVIRONMENT (ENGLAND) - "DEVELOPING STORIES" TV SERIES, 1991-1995 (Box R3199)
    - RF 91042 - TELEVISION TRUST FOR THE ENVIRONMENT (ENGLAND) - "DEVELOPING STORIES" TV SERIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3199)
    - RF 91044 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - URBAN YOUTH CORPS PROGRAMS EVALUATION, 1989-1996; 3 folders. (Box R3200)
    - RF 91044 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - URBAN YOUTH CORPS PROGRAMS EVALUATION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2 folders. (Box R3200)
    - RF 91048 A 6 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - POSTDOCTORAL SCHOLARS AND UNDERCLASS STUDY, 1988-1995 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 141 - WASITO, DR. - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1997 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 148 - NEVHUTALU, AZWITEVHELWI PRINSLOO ? BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1994, 1998 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 150 - NGUYEN VAN UYEN - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 157 - HAN QIDE, 1988-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 159 - KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOW - PIYADA THEERAKULPISUT: FUNCTION OF RICE-ANTHER AND POLLEN SPECIFIC GENES, 1991-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91055 A 160 - INSTITUTE OF BOTANY - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOW - CHEN JING CHUN: MOLECULAR ANALYSIS OF MALE GAMETOGENESIS IN PLANTS, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91068 A 96 - SOE, VALERIE - "THE HOUSE OF ONG", 1991-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91077 A 4 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (CIAT) - FACILITATE TRANSFER OF RICE ANTHER CULTURE FROM CIAT TO LATIN AMERICAN NATIONAL PROGRAMS, 1990-1994, 1997 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91079 A 29 - THAI RED CROSS SOCIETY - COMMERCIAL SEX WORKERS AND HIV TRANSMISSION PILOT STUDY, 1991-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91079 A 33 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - COMMERCIAL SEX WORKERS AND HIV: ETHIOPIA MEXICO, THAILAND, 1991-1993, 1998 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91080 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - PROTOZOAN INTESTINAL DISEASES (SAN FRANCISCO), 1988-1998 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91083 A 100 - POTSDAM COLLEGE OF THE STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - CONCEPTION AND FERTILITY BEHAVIOR IN GHANA, 1991-1996 (Box R3201)
    - RF 91083 A 110 - UNIVERSITY OF KINSHASHA - EMPLOYMENT, EDUCATION AND FERTILITY IN URBAN ZAIRE, 1988-1996 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91083 A 112 - JIMMA INSTITUTE OF HEALTH SCIENCES - INFANT SURVIVAL IN SOUTHWEST ETHIOPIA, 1991-1995 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91083 A 115 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON POPULATION TRAINING, 1992-1995 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91084 A 276 - MALHOTRA, A. - STATUS OF FERTILITY: SRI LANKA WOMEN, 1987-1995 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91084 A 277 - RAMOS, LAURO - DEVELOPMENT OF CHILDREN IN BRAZIL, 1991-1992, 1998 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91084 A 282 - DEMOGRAPHIC RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION, INC. - WOMEN'S STATUS AND FERTILITY - PHILIPPINES, 1992-1995 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91090 A 84 - COUNCIL FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH IN AFRICA (SENEGAL) ? SYMPOSIUM ON CRISES, CONFLICTS AND TRANSFORMATIONS, 1994-1997 (Box R3202)
    - RF 91105 - INVESTMENT FUND FOR FOUNDATIONS ? COMMINGLED INVESTMENT FUND, 1991-1993 (Box R3202)
    - RF 92001 A 151 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL CONSULTATION ON RICE BIOSAFETY IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 1992-1995 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92001 A 164 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - MOLECULAR SIGNALING DURING SYSTEMIC RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1992-1996 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92001 A 168 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RESTRICTION FRAGMENT LENGTH POLYMORPHISM FOR TAGGING RICE GENES, 1991-1997 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92001 A 170 - UNIVERSITY OF PARIS - RICE HOJA BLANCA, 1989-1997 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92003 A 151 - INTERNATIONAL CONSULTATION ON RICE BIOSAFETY IN SOUTH-EAST ASIA, 1991-1994 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92003 A 154 - NANJING UNIVERSITY - VISITING SCIENTIST RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN RICE GENETIC ENGINEERING, 1992-1995, 1998 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92003 A 155 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY - QUANTITATIVE TRAIT LINKAGE (QTL) ANALYSIS IN LOWLAND RICE, 1992-1996 (Box R3203)
    - RF 92006 A 22 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - STOVER PLACEMENT ON SOIL PROPERTIES AND PROCESSES ON MAIZE PRODUCTION, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 65 - SHANGHAI ACADEMY OF SOCIAL SCIENCES - STUDY FERTILITY AMONG CHINESE MINORITIES, 1993-1994 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 68 - UNIVERSITY OF DAR ES SALAAM - FAMILY PLANNING AMONG RURAL TANZANIANS, 1992-1996 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 69 - CARDENAS SANKEN, GUILLERMO HUGO, 1989-1996 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 71 - NATIONAL SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH COUNCIL - (ARGENTINA) - EFFECTS OF PROGESTERONE ON DOPAMINE RELEASE IN BASAL GANGLIA, 1993-1995 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 73 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CORDOBA - IDENTIFY MOLECULES INVOLVED IN SPERM EGG FUSION, 1994-1997 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92014 A 74 - ALL-INDIA INSTITUTE OF MEDICAL SCIENCES ? ROLE OF CYTOKINES IN RHESUS MONKEY, 1991-1994 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92015 A 3 - COUNCIL ON RENEWABLE ENERGY EDUCATION (CREE) - INTERNATIONAL FUND FOR RENEWABLE ENERGY AND ENERGY EFFICIENCY (IFREE), 1991-1998 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92015 A 9 - TALLERES OVIDIO MARTINEZ, SA (TOMSA) - CONVENTIONAL AND ADVANCED MEMBRANES FOR TREATMENT OF SUGARCANE STILLAGE, 1992-1997 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92015 A 2 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS - AUTONOMY OF AFRICAN MUSEUMS, 1992-1996 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92019 A 69 - CENTER FOR AFRICAN ART - "SECRECY: AFRICAN ART THAT CONCEALS AND REVEALS", 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92019 A 71 - INSTITUTE OF CONTEMPORARY ART - "THE TETHERED SHADOW", 1990-1996 (Box R3204)
    - RF 92030 A 104 - DADE FOUNDATION - TEACHER EDUCATION CENTER HUMANITIES PROGRAM, 1987-1996; 3 folders. (Box R3205)
    - RF 92036 - INDEPENDENT COMMISSION ON POPULATION, 1991-1997 (Box R3205)
    - RF 92037 A 13 - COMMITTEE OF SOVIET SCIENTISTS (RUSSIA) - LEAD NATIONAL PROGRAM IN THE CIS, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 265 - EZEALOR, AUGUSTINE- ADIA: INTEGRATED AVIAN PEST DAMAGE IN NIGERIA, 1991-1997 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 271 - MAYOYA. MARIE-ADIA: SECONDARY SCHOOLING IN BURUNDI, 1991-1997 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 275 - KIMENYE, LYDIA - ADIA: ECONOMIC ANALYSIS OF KENYA'S FLOWER EXPORTS, 1991-1998 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 303 - BAKARR, MOHAMED - ADIA: SEEDLING REGENERATION IN WEST AFRICAN RAINFOREST, 1991-1998 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 315 - OGOL, CALLISTUS - ADIA: AGROFORESTRY IN KENYA, 1992-1997 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 319 - BROOKS, SHIRLEY - ADIA: AGRICULTURE IN NATAL, 1940-1990, 1992-1997 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038 A 327 - MUTAMBU, SUSAN - ADIA: PLASMODIUM FALCIPARUM AND HIV IN ZIMBABWEAN PREGNANT WOMEN, 1992-1998 (Box R3206)
    - 920038-419 - RUGUTT, JOSEPH- ADIA: CONTROL OF WITCHWEED, 1992-1998 (Box R3206)
    - 920038-433 - KAGWANJA, JOAN - ADIA: LINKING POPULATION, DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENT IN KENYA, 1993-1997 (Box R3206)
    - RF 92038-438 - MUTONGI, KENDA - ADIA: HISTORY OF MARAGOLI WIDOWHOOD IN WESTERN KENYA, 1993-1998 (Box R3206)
    - 920038-439 - ZULU, ELIYA - ADIA: REPRODUCTIVE BEHAVIOR IN MALAWI, 1994-1997 (Box R3206)
    - 920038-441 - FRED-MENSAH, BEN - ADIA: PROPERTY RIGHTS TRANSITION IN GHANA, 1994-1998 (Box R3206)
    - 920038-445 - ADIH, WILLIAM KOFI - ADIA: CONDOM USE AND HIV INFECTION AMONG UNMARRIED YOUTH IN GHANA, 1994-1998 (Box R3207)
    - 920038-449 - MARALACK, DAVID - ADIA: SQUATIER MOVEMENTS IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1994-1997 (Box R3207)
    - 920038-460 - KYEM, PETER - ADIA: ALTERNATIVE INSITUTIONS FOR RESOURCE MANAGEMENT - SOUTH-WESTERN GHANA, 1993-1997 (Box R3207)
    - 920038-462 - MBATIA, PAUL - ADIA: HEALTH CARE IN KENYA, 1994-1997 (Box R3207)
    - RF 92039 - WISCONSIN PROJECT ON NUCLEAR ARMS CONTROL - NUCLEAR NON-PROLIFERATION, 1990-1995 (Box R3207)
    - RF 92047 - MINORITY VOTER PARTICIPATION, 1990-1993 (Box R3207)
    - RF 92047 - MINORITY VOTER PARTICIPATION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3207)
    - RF 92055 A 68 - LOW, JAN WAYLAND - POTATO IN THE FOOD SYSTEMS OF EASTERN AND CENTRAL AFRICA, 1992-1998 (Box R3207)
    - RF 92055 A 69 - PRICE, LISA MARIE LEIMAR - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP, 1992-1997 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92055 A 70 - MILLS, BRADFORD FRANKLIN - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP: ASSIST KARl, 1992-1997 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92055 A 71 - BERGON, GILLES - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP: SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT OF CENTRAL AMERICAN HILLSIDES, 1992-1997 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92055 A 72 - GAVIAN, SARAH - SSRF: RESOURCE USE IN CROP-LIVESTOCK IN ETHIOPIA, 1992-1997 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92058 A 3 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (CIMMYT} - N-EFFICIENT MAIZE IN MOZAMBIQUE, MALAWI AND ZIMBABWE, 1992-1995 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 163 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOW HERNAN E. LARA: POLYCYSTIC OVARIAN SYNDROME, 1991-1996 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 164 - ADDIS ABABA UNIVERSITY - TECHNIQUES FOR OPTIMIZING PHOTOSYNTHETIC EFFICIENCY OF C4 ORGANISMS, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 165 - UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN - OVARIAN CANCER STUDY BY DR. OBIODUN O. ILESANMI, 1992-1996 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 166 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL AUTONOMA DE MEXICO - STUDY OF CELLULAR MECHANISMS of GnRH PULSES, 1991-1996 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 167 - PONDICHERRY UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENE CLONING FOR MOLT-INHIBITING HORMONE FROM CRUSTACEAN SPECIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 168 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - COWPEA APHIDBORNE MOSAIC POTYVIRUS PROTECTION, 1991-1996 (Box R3208)
    - RF 92059 A 175 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - STRUCTURAL AND MECHANISTIC STUDIES ON 5-LIPOXYGENASE, 1991-1996 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92059 A 176 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLLOWSHIP FOR RAMESH CHANDRA, 1992-1996 (Box R3209)
      Scope and Contents note
      RESCINDED
    - RF 92059 A 178 - JAWAHARLAL NEHRU UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENE AMPLIFICATION AND DRUG RESISTANCE IN LEISHMANIA, 1992-1998 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92059 A 181 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - DNA-PROTEIN INTERACTIONS, 1991-1998 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92059 A 182 - GUANGXI AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - INTERACTION BETWEEN RICE PLANT AND XANTHOMONAS ORYZAE, 1992-1996 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92060 A 8 - SICHUAN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - CROP GENETIC MAPPING/APOMIXIS FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1996 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92060 A 9 - LIAONING ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES (CHINA) - CROP GENETIC MAPPING/SORGHUM FELLOWSHIP, 1992-1998 (Box R3209)
    - RF 92060 A 14 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - CROP GENETIC MAPPING/SORGHUM FELLOWSHIP, 1992-1996 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92072 A 140 - FAGERSTROM, PATRICIO RIQUELME - "WHITE FEAR DISORDER", 1994-1995 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92081 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - TROPICAL FORESTS MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS, 1990-1996 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92085 A 31 - CHINA - PUBLIC HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) ? IMMUNOGENICITY OF JE VACCINE, 1992-1994 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92086 A 11 - NAGAYA, SHOKO - CHILDREN'S VACCINE STUDY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1993-1995, 1998 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92087 A 14 - UNITED NATIONS - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - NORPLANT IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1986-1996 (Box R3210)
    - RF 92090 - UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - ECONOMIC DEMOGRAPHY, 1975-1996; 4 folders. (Box R3211)
    - RF 92090 - UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - ECONOMIC DEMOGRAPHY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2 folders. (Box R3211)
    - RF 92092 A 50 - UNIVERSITY OF DARES SALAAM - HIV-1 INFECTION AMONG WOMEN, 1990-1996 (Box R3212)
    - RF 92092 A 56 - NETWORK OF AIDS RESEARCHERS OF EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (NARESA) - REGIONAL AIDS ACTIVITIES, 1992-1995 (Box R3212)
    - RF 92092 A 66 - MOROCCO - PUBLIC HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - EIGHTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AIDS AND STD, 1992-1998 (Box R3212)
    - RF 92092 A 67 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN FRANCISCO) - CULTURAL DIFFERENCES ON AIDS CONTROL CONFERENCE IN CHIANG MAl, 1993-1994 (Box R3212)
    - RF 92092 A 69 - TIDES FOUNDATION - FUNDERS CONCERNED ABOUT AIDS INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM, 1993-1996 (Box R3212)
    - RF 92092 A 70 - AIDS SUPPORT ORGANISATION (TASO) - TRADITIONAL HEALERS AND AIDS PREVENTION IN GHANA, 1991-1997 (Box R3212)
    - 920092-76 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - DIP. STICK ASSAY FOR HIV SCREENING, 1987-1997 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92093 A 11 - SATHEL - USINAS TERMO E HIDRO ELECTRICAS S.A. (BRAZIL) - BIOMASS-TO-ENERGY PROJECTS IN THE AMAZON REGION, 1993-1995, 1998 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92094 A 20 - OMOLOLU, OBAFEMI - RE-ENTRY GRANT: SCHOOL EFFECT ON NIGERIAN FEMALES, 1992-1995, 1998 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92094 A 30 - MUKKUKA, LAWRENCE - RURAL HOME ENVIRONMENT AND FEMALE SCHOOL ACHIEVEMENT, 1992-1998 (Box R3213)
    - 920094-53 - FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION - DONORS WORKING GROUP 1994 GENEVA MEETING, 1994, 1998 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92095 A 27 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - CHILDREN'S PROBLEM SOLVING AND TEACHER SUPPORT, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box R3213)
    - 920095-37 - ERINOSHO, STELLA YEMISI, 1990-1994 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92099 A 124 - TEATRO DE LA ESPERANZA - "ROSITA'S TRAVELING JALAPENO KITCHEN", 1992-1997 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92092 A 73 - INTERNATIONAL HIV/AIDS ALLIANCE (ENGLAND) - PREVENT SPREAD OF AIDS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1994-1996 (Box R3213)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY, 1980-1997; Multiple folders. (Box R3214)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY, 1980-1997; Multiple folders. (Box R3215)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY, 1980-1997; Multiple folders. (Box R3216)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, Multiple folders. (Box R3217)